<entries>
<entry name="NEXT">Next</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_9">New York is the city that never sleeps and where your money won&apos;t either. If you open a supermarket here, success is guaranteed.</entry>
<entry name="SUBTITLE">Grand opening!</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_11">Humans already inhabit two planets in the solar system, and your supermarket will be the only one available here in Mars.</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_11">Mars</entry>
<entry name="SOLD">Sold!</entry>
<entry name="NEW_MARKET_OPENING">New Supermarket</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_10">The Moon</entry>
<entry name="OLD">Old</entry>
<entry name="CURRENT">Current</entry>
<entry name="OPENING">Opening</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_8">Hong Kong is one of the largest commercial points between China and the rest of the world.  Here your business will be among the most important in the world.</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_9">New York</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_8">Hong Kong</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_7">Tokyo</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_6">London</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_5">Paris</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_4">Beverly Hills</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_3">Miami Beach</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_2">Small city</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_1">Small village</entry>
<entry name="TITLE_0">Residential area</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_0">A quiet, sparsely populated area. Customer demand is basic, but your business will still grow incrementally.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_1">A more urbanized area. Customer demand is more varied, so your earnings will be higher.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_2">With a larger population you get customers that are ready to spend more money.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_3">Miami is a popular tourist area where you will find people with considerable purchasing power.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_4">Beverly Hills is one of world&apos;s most affluent areas. Your earnings here will be considerable.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_5">Paris, the city of light, is a multicultural city with customers of all kinds. You will make a fortune here.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_10">Civilization has evolved so much that we now populate the moon! We need to quickly establish the first lunar supermarket.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_7">Tokyo is a massive city. With so many customers and so much to sell, your supermarket will conquer the Land of the Rising Sun.</entry>
<entry name="DESCRIPTION_6">London is a major world city and the perfect place to open a highly profitable supermarket.</entry>
</entries>
