<entries>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_4_PRE_2">The cashier charges customers for the products they want to buy. The checkout process is a bit slow, but you&apos;ll be able to improve it soon.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_6">Let&apos;s improve the produce department and increase our profit. Tap it!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_1">Hey! There you are, boss. We finished building the supermarket, so we&apos;re now ready for the grand opening. We were waiting for you!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_19">But now, we should focus on the produce department while making sure the cash registers and parking lot run smoothly. That&apos;ll make us more money in a hurry!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_7">Improving the produce department will give us more money per customer.</entry>
<entry name="CHARACTER_NAME">Assistant</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_5">Right now, we only have a produce department, but we&apos;ll expand the business step by step.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_30">As you can see, it&apos;s really worth doing... although it doesn&apos;t have to be now. You can build a new supermarket when you&apos;re ready.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_4_PRE_1">Look, the customer is shopping in the produce department.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_18">Tap the office to see all the different departments you can build and really make the supermarket grow.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_8">Oh no! The parking lot is full. We need to fix this to accommodate more customers</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_28">But, since the new supermarket will be in a city with more people and more money, we&apos;ll get more revenue from each sale.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_26">Building a new supermarket has many advantages.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_27">Opening a new supermarket in another city means we&apos;ll have to build all the departments again.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_9">Tap the parking sign.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_25">We have earned enough money to build a new supermarket in a bigger city! It&apos;ll make us earn more money.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_22">Boss, we can now build a bakery in the supermarket!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_23">Great! Now our clients can buy more products, and we&apos;ll make more money with each purchase.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_20">If everything goes well, we&apos;ll be able to open a new supermarket in a bigger city.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_21">I&apos;m off to attend to some unresolved business. You&apos;re in charge now, boss!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_24">Good news, boss!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_3">Look! The customer just parked the car, taking one parking space. Customers will keep coming, so let&apos;s now see how the shopping works out.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_2">Our first customer should be here soon. I&apos;m so excited!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_29">We could earn 50 times more from the produce department in the new city than we do now.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_16">Oh! I almost forgot about the home delivery trucks. Tap them to collect the money from the home delivery service.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_17">Excellent. The business is growing!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_14">Let&apos;s build a new cash register to assist more customers. This will reduce the line and we can cash in faster. Tap the cash register.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_15">Perfect. Now we can take care of customers faster, so they won&apos;t have to wait so long.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_12">Great, that&apos;s enough for now.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_13">Oops! It seems we have problems helping the customers. They shouldn&apos;t have to wait that long!</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_10">Fantastic! We doubled the number of parking spaces. Now there is space for more customers.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_11">But if we want more customers, we have to invest in advertising. Tap the button.</entry>
<entry name="TUTORIAL_4">Great! Our first sale!</entry>
</entries>
